Yes, its again time for such a video.
Today we look at the CDU
also a bit on SPD and AFD
but primarily we look at the CDU.
In the last few weeks, I and TJ, we cherry-picked some interesting topics
and looked, what's the CDU doing there.
What's their opinion?
To tell the truth:
Fuck is that heavy.
I didn't know, that it's so heavy.
In this video, I will show,
how CDU-members are lying,
the lack of fundamental competences needed for their job,
how they doing politics against expert opinions,
how they evidently participate at different war crimes,
how they use propaganda and falsehoods against the young generation,
how the rich are benefiting from their politic over the last decades
and how the others lose more and more
and I will show
that, according to the expert opinion of thousands of german scientists,
the CDU, contemporary, is destroying our live and our future.
As I always do, I will proof all that in detail.
You know, when I'm doing such a video, I'm doing it well..
Next weekend are the EU-elections.
I hope you all will vote
I won't only refer to EU-politics
because EU-politics is fucking boring * at least often *
and above all you can't easily separate it.
If you vote for a party at EU-level
than you are bolstering them on national level.
So you can't separate that.
This video isn't going to be a boring political video.
This time, it's going to be a destruction-video.
Not because I'm actively trying to destroy someone,
but because the facts are supporting,
that the CDU is destroying themselves, their reputation and their election result.
First, we look at the result of decades of CDU-intensive politics
and who is benefiting.
* winners and losers *
Two things before the start:
1. If I'm saying CDU in this video,
I'm meaning CDU and/or CSU.
The CSU is, in simple terms, the Bavarian CDU.
Together they are forming the "Union"-party.
Because it's easier, I'm calling them CDU.
2. I have so fucking many proofs in this video,
that I'm not shortening them
to an abbreviation,
like here,
and in the description is a list with sources, identified by the abbreviations
Let's start.
* For whom is the CDU doing politics? *
For whom is the CDU doing actually politics?
On their homepage they are stating,
that they are doing politics for all classes
and that they are the people's party of the political center. * Self-conception of the CDU - The Christian Democratic Union is the peoples party of the political center. We address people from all classes and groups from our country. The basis for our is the Christian understanding of humans *
But are they that really?
Lets check that.
In the last 36 years, the CDU was 29 years in power.
That means: If the were good
doing politics for all classes of society
we should notice that in statistics.
In this period the gap between rich and poor widened.
* As you can see, the SPD-governed years weren't better * The poorest 50% have less and less money
and the richest 10% more and more money.
* Development of poverty and economy 2006-2013 * In addition the poverty in Germany increased is increasing constantly in recent years.
and it doesn't look like it's changing in the near future.
In addition, most of the rich doesn't get rich by working hard,
but by inheritances and gifts.
So the children of rich parents simply inherit good - and done.
A few decades ago, it was different.
their wealth was elaborated by themselves.
That's different now.
Today, the most isn't elaborated by themselves,
but comes by a lucky inheritance.
Fun fact:
The 45 richest private households
the same asset as the poorest 50%. * Distribution of assets in Germany *
That are over 40 people.
Such things didn't happen random.
The government,
in this period especially the CDU,
has many capabilities
to influence such things.
For example, the prerequisites were adjusted
so that the poor have to bear a higher tax burden than 20 years ago.
* change of tax burden of different income groups 2015 vs 1998 * And the rich people have to bear less tax burden than 20 years ago.
Obviously such adjustments contribute to such developments.
In the last decades, the super rich have benefited from CDU
where as the poor lost.
But ey: CDU - the party for all classes.
Equal opportunities are one of the most important things of growing inequality.
That means: What you achieve in your live
shouldn't depend on your parent's wealth, educational level or anything else.
So even if you're from a poorer household,
you should have, through education and such things,
the same chances as everyone else, to get rich
or get a good job.
The problem is: promotion prospects through education
is in Germany much lower than in most other industrial countries.
In the PISA study, we lost in categories like
social background or migrant background.
This stresses the unfairness.
That means: In Germany
you are getting rich, if your father * or your mother * is rich.
But ey: CDU - a party for all classes.
While we are on education:
Germany spends categorical less money on education then other industrial countries. * Germany spends comparatively little on education - Education spending in percent of GDP 2015 *
So we are below the average.
Even though much associations and institutions
are demanding much more money for education,
because we have, for example, an extreme teacher shortage
and our schools are falling apart.
Now one could say: Education depends on the federal state.
Correct, but in the federal states, where the CDU is in the government,
is spend less money per pupil on education
than in other federal states. * Expenditures per pupil *
Great, CDU, great.
But OK, Merkel has now announced
to spend 10% of the GDP on education and research.
Oh, she wanted to do that until 2015?
She didn't stuck to it? Not even half? * before 8,4% ; status as of 2015 ; target 2015 10% *
Wow, there is someone really good in managing things.
Conclusion: In the last decades, the CDU had the most power
and the result is,
that lots of things developed good
and for all other not so good.
That's sober seen the result of the course of the CDU.
Education doesn't have a high priority for them.
That's also not a rating, but a sober conclusion of the data.
But ey: CDU - a party for all classes.
Well, let's finish with the economic topic.
Economy is a little bit boring.
Do you know, what's exciting? Living.
I love to live.
I need a lot for living.
But above all, the most important is a functioning earth.
The next topic is climate.
A few weeks ago, I thought global warming isn't going to be optimal,
but it's not going to get crap.
Than I researched.
And what I found out, was fucking heavy.
* The climate crisis - How the CDU destroys our life *
Some might say: This title,
CDU is destroying our live, that's exaggerated a little bit.
Yes, a few weeks ago, I have thought so, too.
The majority of experts and scientists
are sharing this exact opinion and can proof this pretty good.
But before we look at their proofs for the failure of CDU and SPD,
we have to clarify the current status.
* The current status *
It's going to be hot. 2018 was the fourth warmest year since records began.
Now, you maybe say: The fourth warmest? Than there were three years warmer.
Yes. Do you know which? 2015, 2016 and 2017.
That means: The last four years
were the four warmest years in history. lol.
The consequences are quite clear.
Due to global warming natural disasters are on the rise,
their consequences and dimensions are on the rise.
This costs currently directly hundreds of billions per year.
Whole regions are sunk already.
Because of this, there are lots of millions of refugees,
who have lost their home and have to be accommodated anywhere else.
A few weeks age, Ju was in Bangladesh
and spoke with such people.
That was part of his video.
Furthermore species are becoming extinct hundred times faster.
We lose complete habitats, like coral reefs.
Biologists are saying, that a new mass extinction is probable.
The last one was 66 million years ago.
Then an asteroid with the size of a large city crashed on earth.
Today we are able to do it alone.
That all happened,
because it got in average one degree warmer.
That would remain so for hundreds or thousands of years,
even if mankind would stop burning fuel and coal tomorrow.
And who is thinking: Do one or two degrees  make such a huge difference?
I can say them: Yes, they do.
Or in different words:
Many are thinking: one degree, two degree, three degree - What's the difference?
As physician I can say you: It's making a huge difference, if you have 41 degree fever or 43 degree fever.
The first one is compatible with life, the second one not.
OK, that' the current status.
But, who is to blame for that?
* Who is to blame? *
I'm not going into physical details.
Primarily this is happening through CO2 and methane. * Share of different gases on global warming - CO2, methane, other *
The more of this gases is in atmosphere, the warmer it's going to be.
Methane is produced primarily by industrial animal husbandry .
Due to the lack of time, I won't talking about methane,
because CO2 is the largest factor for global warming.
Because of that I'm explaining primarily that.
CO2 is a little part of the air
and that's no problem.
Leaves, for example, absorb CO2 and emit CO2, for example when they rot.
That means: There exists different points in nature, where CO2 is emitted.
But, that was previously absorbed from air.
That means: There is not more CO2 in the world due to rotting leaves.
If it rains, there is not suddenly more water in the world.
That are natural cycles
and the amount of CO2 allways remains the same.
Because of that, the amount of CO2
remained quite the same.
So the problem is not, that CO2 exists, but that it increases.
Who to blame?
We. Completely.
The rise of carbon dioxide in atmosphere,
which is now at 75%,
is 100% caused by humans.
That's completely indisputable in science.
Primarily we are doing this by digging for coal, oil and natural gas and burning it.
That's inside this and so this shit gets into the air.
That means:  Global warming is caused by 100% by humans.
And we still have the power to simply stop this.
Above all by stopping the digging and burning.
And now there are, by 100%, some people among you,
who are saying: Eh, I've heard:
There is a bit scientific disagreement about that.
That's not so sure... Is mankind so hard to blame for... Do they agree on...
Yes, OK. Let's look, how agreed they are.
tHE scIenCe doEs'nT agReE
I've asked this question to climate scientists.
So I called this Institutes
and they said: Ey, there is no serious scientist
who is arguing the converse.
I: Really?
And they: Yes, there are maybe some, who were payed by oil industry,
but normally no serious scientist will do that.
And that's in line with the numbers: Only 0.7% of the scientific publications claimed, that mankind isn't to blame for.  * "[...] 0.7 % denied the human caused climate change and 0.3% weren't sure, what's the reason for global warming." *
Further analysis showed:
That are individual persons who are publishing this.
There exists no reputable institutes or national academies who claim this. * "Not one national academy desputes or denies the scientific consensus regarding the human caused climate change" *
Not a fucking single one.
Furthermore studies have shown, that the public extremely underestimates, how big this consensus is.
So how strong the science agrees.
And there are studies showing, that:
The sooner you say: "Mankind isn't to blame for climate change.",
the sooner you don't know what you're talking about.
So, realtalk:
Before my research, I didn't know how big this consensus is.
I thought, something like 98, 97%. But no, it is more and unbelievable clear.
The AFD is the only political party, who denies this.
Yes. Did you thought, They get nothing?
No, no. Nobody should draw wrong conclusions from this video
and think, the AFD could be a legit option.
They aren't. Not only, because there are Nazis, but also, because they aren't cognitive impressive.
They seriously think, that the thousands of scientists on the world aren't serious.
Sometimes, they say, that the scientist are lying, that's not correct, what the scientists are saying.
And mankind isn't to blame for climate change.
Because climate change isn't caused by mankind. * Speaker for science and finance of the parliamentary group of the AFD *
This woman claims, that global warming is maybe caused by sun. Maybe the sun is shining stronger.
Maybe the thousands of climate scientists didn't have done their job correctly and never examined this.
News flash: I've literally googled this one minute and found various papers who examined this and found out the opposite. * "Since 1940 the activity of the sun was in average constant, in the last decades  even declining" *
So the sun is shining less strong. lol.
Yes, you find that funny.
But do you know, whats even more funny?
On the question of weather that should be a stronger reason for doing something against climate change, she answers:
We should explain to the sun, that she should shine less, for example.
That would be a consideration, because the sun has an effect to the oceans and not we onto the oceans, but the sun.
Now the few AFD voters following me are rightly ashamed.
But, it's not bad. You're responsible for her sitting in the German parliament
and making us happy with such wisdom, but you don't need to repeat your mistake.
Than nobody is angry at you.
But, what about the CDU?
Well, they are surely more compentent?
They wouldn't simply ignore clear scientific facts and an overwhelming consensus about necessary behaviour?
Didn't they?
Well, before going into this, we have to look shortly on what the science is saying, in addition to blame mankind.
* What do we have to do? *
Because of the global rise of average 1°C, all the catastrophes came.
The scientific community  agrees that we must not exceed 1.5°C.
If we exceed 1.5°C it is extremely likely that we are getting into a feedback loop.
In this case it is getting warmer, no matter what we are doing.
That's then irreversible - You can't undo that.
In other words: We would have destroyed earth.
The world is fucked up for your children, grandchildren and even for your great great great great great grandchildren.
They wold never again see the earth like we have got familiar with.
Or saying it with a scientific slang:
The irreversibility of the change of ecological systems in their regeneration, in my opinion, haven't been understood.
How is earth looking like, if we get into this feedback loop?
Well, because of the lost of their homes, 100 millions of people have to flee.
A few years ago, the International Organization for Migration has calculated, that in 30 years 230 million people have to find accomodation in different countries.
Since then we weren't on such a good course.
Because of that, the IOM assumes, that there will be over 400 million displaced persons.
Only for an order of magnitude:
There are living 500 million people in the EU.
Only that you know that.
So many people will come and many of them to europe.
So, if you believe, that the refugees in recent years were a "refugee crisis", you can look forward to this.
Then there won't be a few million people, but there will be hundreds of millions of people.
And you won't be able to say to them:
Rebuild your home.
This would not be possible anymore.
You remember:
Irreversability
So: No reconstruction and no roll back.
So: The earth will get warmer and warmer and we cannot do something against that.
There will be increasingly grosser and stronger natural catastrophes.
The food suply in lots of countries will go out.
Probably there will be more wars on ressources.
The announced mass extinction would no longer be stoppable.
But not only animals are dying.
We will also receive a little goodie bag.
There will be more diseases for us.
Most of all more infectious diseases and allergies.
Yippee.
Ok, it sound's like this topic should have an inconceivable high priority for every politician.
But, can we still change this?
* What can we do? *